{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Kuhn",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Cincinnati",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8934199810028076,
            "question": "Where was Thomas Kuhn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440645098686218,
            "question": "What year was Thomas Kuhn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4636061191558838,
            "question": "What is Thomas Kuhn known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31831255555152893,
            "question": "In what city did Thomas Kuhn live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24680082499980927,
            "question": "What university did Thomas Kuhn attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23010195791721344,
            "question": "Was Thomas Kuhn a physicist or a philosopher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21518360078334808,
            "question": "What concept did Thomas Kuhn introduce in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19568777084350586,
            "question": "What field of study is Thomas Kuhn associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1483107954263687,
            "question": "Name one significant book written by Thomas Kuhn."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1096000000834465,
            "question": "What impact did Thomas Kuhn's ideas have on scientific thinking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7992_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one significant book written by Thomas Kuhn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7992_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Thomas Kuhn associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7992_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What concept did Thomas Kuhn introduce in his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7992_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7992_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7992/re-ranker-msmarco/91.txt`, `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7992/re-ranker-msmarco/79.txt`, `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7992/re-ranker-msmarco/95.txt`, and `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7992/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt` all mention Thomas Kuhn's birthplace as Cincinnati, Ohio.\n* The document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7992/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt` also confirms his birthplace as Cincinnati, Ohio.\n* Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple \"Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently mention that Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati, Ohio. Therefore, the statement \"Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}